Joseph C. Mele collection of dialect recordings from the University of South Alabama
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Dialect recordings by geographic area, 1975-1980
  - Subseries 1. United States spoken English, 1975-1980
    - Louisiana: Acadian area, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR103; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Odric Ortego. LA(FR)CM75. Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: Hammond, August 17, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR104; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Celia D. Mele, birthdate: December 23, 1911. LACF79 (1911). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: LaFourche Parish, April 3, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR105; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Clement Durocher, birthdate: August 19, 1903. LA(Acad)CM77 (1903). Agent: Stephen Cooper.
    - Louisiana: New Iberia, December 29, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR106; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Daniel Polk, birthdate: February 28, 1945. LACM78 (1945). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: New Orleans, February 23, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR107; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Katherine Vincent, birthdate: 1979. LACF79 (1917). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: New Orleans, November 7, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR108; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dolly Gene S. Mele, birthdate: February 14, 1932. LACF78 (1932). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: New Orleans, February 26, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR109; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Linda Lear, birthdate: 1948. LACF79 (1948). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: New Orleans, February 28, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR110; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lyddia Lear, birthdate: 1966. LACF79 (1966). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: Terrebonne Parish, July 3, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR111; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Elda Bergeron, birthdate: August 22, 1886. LACF76 (1886). Acadian (Cajun). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: Washington Parish, October 25, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR112; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Richard Magee, birthdate: August 28, 1937. LACM77 (1937). Agent: H. Spicer.
    - Louisiana: St. Germain Parish, November 26, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR113; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dolly B., birthdate: 1905. LACF76 (1985). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, November, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR114; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Harold A. Shafer, birthdate: May 16, 1987. MDCM76 (1887). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, November, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR115; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Leroy G. Messersmith, birthdate: October 18, 1888. MDCM76 (1888). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, May 25, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR116; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Louisa Hare, birthdate: March 2, 1894. MDCF77 (1894). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, May 15, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR117; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frederick Goetz, birthdate: June 9, 1894. MDCM77 (1894). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR118; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded November 26, 1976, and January 27, 1977. Ethna P. Lulay, birthdate: January 9, 1895. MDCF76 (1895).
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR119; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 15, 1976, and January 22, 1977. Loretta A. Caster, birth date: March 11, 1898. MDCF76 (1898). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR120; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded November, 1976, and January 27, 1977. Margaret M. Pistel, birth date: October 8, 1900. MDCF76 (1900). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR121; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded November, 1976, and January 28, 1977. Margarite Fields, birthdate: September 26, 1904. MDCF76 (1904). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, November, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR122; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Grace Awalt, birthdate: 1905. MDCF76 (1905). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR123; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded November 27, 1976, and January 27, 1976. Florence P. Carr, birth date: October 16, 1906. MDCF76 (1906). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, April 21, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR205; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Johnny Council, birthdate: February 24, 1908. MDBM76 (1908). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR124; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 12, 1976 and January 21, 1977. Zelda Schrum, birthdate: June 21, 1908. MDCF76 (1908). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR125; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 10, 1976 and January 21, 1977. Warren F. Brunner, birth date: May 2, 1910. MDCM76 (1910). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, November 23, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR126; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Virginia Gann, birthdate: 1910. MDCF79 (1910). Agent: Canuteson.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR127; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 12, 1976 and January 27, 1977. Agnes Wilson, birthdate: December 10, 1911. MDCF76 (1911). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, May 15, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR128; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frank Pelz, birthdate: January 1, 1912. MDCM77 (1912). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, May 15, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR129; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Amelia Tacka, birthdate: June 29, 1912. MDCF77 (1912). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR130; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 12, 1976 and January, 1977. Bernard D. Carmel, birthdate: February 11, 1914. MDCM76 (1914). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, May 26, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR131; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      James Asimakes, birthdate: October 16, 1914. MDCM77 (1914). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR132; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 10, 1976 and January 21, 1977. Ruth L. Gibson, birthdate: October 5, 1915. MDCF76 (1915). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, November, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR133; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Israel Virginia, birthdate: August 25, 1916. MDCF76 (1916). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, December 16, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR134; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Catherine T. Winter, birthdate: February 6, 1916. MDCF76 (1916). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1976-1977, AFC 2015/043: SR135; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded November, 1976 and January 28, 1977. Margaret P. Mace, birthdate: January 15, 1918. MDCF76 (1918). Agent: Bill Wallace.
    - Maryland: Baltimore, November 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR136; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dorothy Kleinkamp, birthdate: April 21, 1928. MDCF79 (1928). Agent: Camieson.
    - Maryland: Federalsburg, October 9, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR137; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edwin J. Rosser, birthdate: 1900. MDCM76 (1900). Agent: John Bronson, Jr.
    - Massachusetts: Lynn, February 25, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR138; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frank Leja, birthdate: October 21, 1958. MACM80 (1958). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Massachusetts: Lynn, February 25, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR139; 1 sound cassette: analog.
    - Massachusetts: Quincy, October 29, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR140; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      William J. Harkins, birthdate: January 23, 1923. MACM79 (1923). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Michigan: Detroit, July 27, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR141; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      David E. Harris, birthdate: November 29, 1962. MICM79 (1962). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Michigan: Kent County, December 12, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR142; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Clara Minderhout, birthdate: February 25, 1890. MICF (1890). Agent: Alice Minderhout.
    - Minnesota: Crookston, February 23, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR143; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Deanna Stainbrook, birthdate: June 16, 1960. MNCF79 (1960). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Minnesota: Duluth, May 18, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR144; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      William Newman, birthdate: 1915. MNCM78 (1915). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Minnesota: Duluth, May 18, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR145; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jerome Thompson, birthdate: May 16, 1934. MNCM78 (1934). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Minnesota: Finnish dialect, January, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR146; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ero H. Selonen, birthdate: July 1, 1942. Born, Tuusniemi, Finland. MNCM78 (1942). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Minnesota: [American] Indian dialect, November 1, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR147; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Harry Lightfeather, birthdate: 1925. MNIM77 (1925). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Minnesota: St. Paul, November, 1974, AFC 2015/043: SR148; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Janice Kerns, birthdate: April 4, 1951. MNCF74 (1951). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Minnesota: Staples, July 12, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR149; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Bonnie Beane, birthdate: June 10, 1957. MNCF79 (1957). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Mississippi: Avery, August 15, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR150; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Doris Crager, birthdate: August 29, 1913. MSCF78 (1913). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Mississippi: Forest, May 23, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR151; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      W.D. Folks, birthdate: November 26, 1921. MSCM78 (1921). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Mississippi: Kosciusko, August 15, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR152; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ethel Leach, birthdate: March 22, 1895. MSCF78 (1895). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Missouri: Dunegan, October 27, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR153; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lero Frazier, birthdate: January 12, 1915. MOCF79 (1915). Agent: Canuteson.
    - Missouri: Grandy County, November 23, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR154; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen Seat, birthdate: November 5, 1910. MOCF79 (1914). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Missouri: Kansas City, November 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR155; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      William D. Haun, birthdate: January 29, 1906. MOCM79 (1906). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Missouri: Kansas City, November 17, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR156; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Shirley B. Reynolds, birthdate: July 9, 1921. MOCF79 (1921). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Missouri: Liberty, November 20, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR157; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Earl Kirkland, birthdate: September 16, 1919. MOCM79 (1919). Agent: J. Canutesen.
    - Missouri: Macon County, November 17, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR158; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen M. Sullivan, birthdate: June 1, 1912. MOCF79 (1912).
    - Missouri: Springfield, November 17, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR159; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      C. Aline Knight, birthdate: September 20, 1920. MOCF79 (1920).
    - Missouri: Springfield, November 22, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR160; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Harley Lawson, birthdate: September 20, 1931. MOCM79 (1931). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Missouri: St. Louis, November 23, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR161; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Vera W. Kohling, birthdate: October 27, 1907. MOCF79 (1907).
    - Montana: Missoula, August 12, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR162; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dee Guilboult, birthdate: November 30, 1895. MTCM76 (1895). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Montana: Missoula, August 12, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR163; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Stella V. Guilbaut, birthdate: December 7, 1910. MTCF76 (1910). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Montana: South Central, August 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR164; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      George Bonawitz, birthdate: September 22, 1935. Billings, Montana. MTCM76 (1935). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Montana: Area unknown, August 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR165; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John Alfred Linn, birthdate: November 18, 1933. Billings, Montana. MTCM76 (1933). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Montana: Western, August 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR166; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Vernie E. Lynn, birthdate: November 17, 1906. Kalispell, Montana. MTCF76 (1906). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - New York: Bronx, September 26, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR167; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      William Pilson, birthdate: October 20, 1914. NYHM76 (1914). Agent: Andrea G. Osburne.
    - New York: Brooklyn, May 29, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR168; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Michael Maretta, birthdate: September 17, 1916. "New Yorkese." NYCM76 (1916). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele (Bill Harris).
    - New York: Buffalo, April 14, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR169; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      David A. Irish, birthdate: July 1, 1944. NYCM76 (1944). Agent: Dr. Parker, NC State.
    - New York: New York City, February 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR170; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lisa Williams, birthdate: December 17, 1957. NYBF79 (1957). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - New York: Poughkeepsie, December 5, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR171; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Anne O'Hehir, birthdate: September 27, 1922. NYCF77 (1922). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - New York: Poughkeepsie, December 16, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR172; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Robin Talbot, birthdate: May 7, 1959. NYCF (1959). Agent: Sheri Sinmerman.
    - New York: Yonkers, August 28, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR173; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Nina D'Ariano; Miss Susan D'Ariano (middle age and young adult). NYCF75. Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - North Carolina: Beaufort, March 9, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR174; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Hugh F. Jones, birthdate: September 17, 1955. NCCM76 (1955). Agent: C.A. Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Carteret County, March 9, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR175; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Louis S. Mason, birthdate: September 1, 1905. NCCF76 (1905). Agent: G.A. Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Cary, March 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR176; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mr. Pat Pleasants, birthdate: February 1, 1904. Wake County, N.C. (East Piedmont). NCCM76 (1904). Agent: C.A. Parker.
    - North Carolina: Cary, March 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR177; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Jaunita Alexander, birthdate: May 26, 1918. Wake County, N.C. NCCF76 (1918)x. Agent: C.A. Parker.
    - North Carolina: Chapel Hill, April 28, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR178; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sidney Gattis, birthdate: August 11, 1904. NCMB76 (1904). Agent: Dr. Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Chatam County, February 27, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR179; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lois Eva Cole, birthdate: September 12, 1896. NCBM76 (1896). Agent: Charles Parker.
    - North Carolina: Chatam County, April 29, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR180; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elizabeth Lewis, birthdate: November 19, 1923. NCBF76 (1923). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Durham County, March 14, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR181; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John Thompson Craig, birthdate: May 22, 1920. NCCM76 (1920). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Durham County, March 14, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR182; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edward Newton, birthdate: March 24, 1922. NCCM76 (1922). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Eastern, March 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR183; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jessie H. Rodgers, birthdate: 1897. NCCF76 (1897). Agent: Dr. Helen Steer, East Carolina University.
    - North Carolina: Eastern, March 17, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR184; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dorothy J. Kelly, birthdate: July 16, 1930. NCCF76 (1930). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Franklin County, 1976-03, AFC 2015/043: SR185; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Allen Jones, recorded March 17, 1976; Cory Lee Richardson, recorded April 30, 1976. birthdate: June 23, 1924. NCBM76 (1924). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker.
    - North Carolina: Gastonia, March 27, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR186; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sena O. Hurdt, birthdate: April 10, 1902. NCCF76 (1902). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Gastonia, March 27, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR187; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Clara Price, birthdate: March 27, 1976. NCCF76 (1923). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: High Point, March 5, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR188; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ella Mae Beaver, birthdate: January 12, 1914. NCCF76 (1914). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Morganton, October 2, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR189; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lucille DuBryne, birthdate: March 25, 1924. NCCF75 (1924). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - North Carolina: Orange County, February 26, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR190; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edward Perry, birthdate: April 15, 1896. NCBM76 (1896). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker by Noreen Strong.
    - North Carolina: Orange County, February 26, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR191; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Hedrick F. Neville, birthdate: February 21, 1898. NCBM76 (1898). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker by Noreen Strong, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Outer Banks, March 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR192; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Brenda Carpenter, birthdate: October 26, 1948. NCCF76 (1948). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Piedmont, February 27, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR193; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Hubert Robinson, birthdate: January 27, 1865?. NCBF76 (1865?). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker by Noreen Strong, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Piedmont, March 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR194; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      David Grimes, birthdate: December 23, 1929. NCCM76 (1929). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Pitt County, April 22, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR195; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Alice Riggs Proctor, birthdate: October 29, 1894. NCCF76 (1894). Agent: Helen Steer, East Carolina University.
    - North Carolina: Robeson County, March 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR196; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Doctor Fuller Lowry, birthdate: January 8, 1881. NCIM76 (1881). Lumbee Indian. Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Robeson County, March 5, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR197; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Timothy Strickland, birthdate: November 11, 1919. NCIM76 (1919). Lumbee Indian. Agent: Dr. Charles Parker.
    - North Carolina: Union County, March 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR198; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Margaret G. Whitley, birthdate: May 18, 1912. NCCF76 (1912). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Wake County, March 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR199; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ernest Choplin, birthdate: April 2, 1908. NCCM76 (1908). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Washington, March 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR200; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Catherine Chesson, birthdate: August 29, 1918. NCCF76 (1918). Agent: Helen Steer, East Carolina University.
    - North Carolina: Wilkes County, March 10, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR201; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John A. Sebastian, birthdate: June 1, 1911. NCCM76 (1911). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Wilkes County, March 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR202; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Anna B. Gambill, birthdate: July 12, 1942. NCCF76 (1942). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Wilmington, March 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR203; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Howard L. Guld, birthdate: April 16, 1930. NCCM76 (1930). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - North Carolina: Wilson, April 25, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR204; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Marzzlar Yates, birthdate: November 25, 1902. NCBF76 (1902). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - Ohio: Cincinnati, April 7, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR206; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Janet Richardson, birthdate: October 29, 1934. OHCF79 (1932). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Ohio: Richland County, January 13, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR207; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nancy Uhlig, birthdate: March 13, 1943. OHCF78 (1943). OHCF78 (1943). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Ohio: Sandusky County, May 19, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR208; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Marian G. Burtscher, birthdate: March 15, 1913. OHCF78 (1913). Woodville, Ohio. Agent: Kenneth Robb.
    - Ohio: Washington County, April 9, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR209; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frieda Faher, birthdate: July 15, 1897. OHCF79 (1897). Agent: G. Evans.
    - Ohio: Washington County, April 10, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR210; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lola Miller, birthdate: July 1, 1911. OHCF79 (1911). Agent: G. Evans.
    - Pennsylvania: Freeport, November 21, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR211; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Robert Kalston, birthdate: April 3, 1916. PACM79 (1916). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Pennsylvania: Jonestown, November 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR212; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mary K. Jones, birthdate: June 19, 1935. PACF79 (1935). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, August 23, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR213; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nellie E. Gustaveson, birthdate: July 2, 1886. PACF77 (1886). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, August 1, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR214; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Donald F. Hopkins, Sr., birthdate: October 2, 1890. PACM77 (1890). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, August 23, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR215; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elizabeth B. Thompson, birthdate: July 21, 1896. PACF77 (1896). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, August 23, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR216; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Harriet N. Humphries, birthdate: November 5, 1899. PACF77 (1899). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, August 23, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR217; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Warrenita W. Leech, birthdate: January 15, 1904. PACF77 (1904). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, July 17, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR218; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frank J. Strassner, Jr., birthdate: April 16, 1908. PACM77 (1908). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, December 9, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR219; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Clyde M. Wilson, birthdate: January 8, 1934. PABM80 (1934).
    - Pennsylvania: Scranton, April 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR220; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Theodore Williams, birthdate: July 14, 1924. PACM78 (1924). Agent: Helene Fuller.
    - Pennsylvania: Shamokin, June 10, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR221; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Louis J. Perotti, birthdate: November 11, 1903. PACM78 (1903). Agent: Mary Alice Minderhout.
    - Pennsylvania: Upper Darby, January 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR222; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lillian Luedecke, birthdate: June 15, 1908. PACF78 (1908). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Upper Darby, January 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR223; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Joan Massimini birthdate: August 19, 1930. PACF78 (1930). Agent: Carolyn Keefe.
    - Pennsylvania: Upper Darby, January 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR224; 1 sound cassette: analog.
    - Pennsylvania: Washington Township, September 9, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR225; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Cora Hasson, birthdate: October 28, 1903. PACF78 (1903). Agent: Mary Alice Minderhout.
    - Pennsylvania: Waynesboro, December 10, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR226; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elizabeth Brunner, birthdate: July 19, 1916. PAHF76 (1916). Agent: Bill Wallace.